
Function: setPage( stringHashTag, stringOptionalPageTitle)

Description: Sets a new hash tagged page url for permalinks and bookmarking.

Returns: Null.

Note: When a hash tag is set, the associated DC object will automatically be rendered when the page loads by referencing the DC object's matching id. To enable this functionality, the trackPage property must be set to true within the corresponding DC object setup declaration. Additionally, the setPage() function will add the modified URL to the browser history to enable Back and Forward button navigation.

Example:

( Starting address bar: https://whatsock.com/ )

// Set a hash tag for the page that matches the DC object id "AutomationTab"

$A.setPage("AutomationTab", "Automation Instructions");

( Changed address bar: https://whatsock.com/#AutomationTab )

If bookmarked or shared, the DC object with the matching id "AutomationTab" will automatically render when the page loads. This will work for any type of DC object, such as tabs, accordion panels, dialogs, or anything else.

IMPORTANT: To enable this functionality, the trackPage property must be set to true within the setup declaration for the DC object.
For more details, see: Help/DC API/DC Object Configuration/Behaviors
