
Boolean: isAnimating

Description: Determines if an animation effect is currently running as part of a DC object lifecycle method.

Returns: True if yes, False otherwise.

Note: This property is only set when a valid animation effect is active within a DC object declaration. For further details, see: 
Help/DC API/DC Object Configuration/Visual Effects

Example:

// Is an animation effect currently running on a DC object?

alert($A.isAnimating);
