
Function: isHidden(domElement)

Description: Checks if the specified DOM node is hidden.

Returns: True if yes, False otherwise.

Note: The isHidden() function will not determine that offscreen content is hidden. A DOM node will only be confirmed as hidden if it, or one of its ancestors, includes the hidden attribute or is hidden using CSS display:none or visibility:hidden. Similarly, the attribute aria-hidden="true" will not be confirmed as hidden.

Example:

// Verify if the specified DOM node is hidden.
var isHidden = $A.isHidden(domElement);

// Or

var isHidden = $A(domElement).isHidden();
