
Function: showBackground()

Description: restores background content to the accessibility tree so that screen reader users can once again perceive it during navigation.

Returns: domElement, or $A object if chained.

Note: The showBackground() function has no impact on visual layout, but will instead restore background content that was previously hidden from non-sighted screen reader users via the hideBackground() function.

Example:

// Restore the background content so that it is once again perceivable and navigable for non-sighted screen reader users.

$A.showBackground();
