
Function: setDisabled(domElementOrCSSSelector, boolDisableState)

Description: Sets the disabled state of any native or simulated active element.

Returns: Original Object, or $A object if chained.

Note: Meant to accompany the isDisabled() and updateDisabled() functions. When a DC object is passed as the first parameter, the disabled state of its triggering element will be set in addition to the internal disabled state of the DC object. All native form fields that support the disabled property will have the disabled property set accordingly, and all links and simulated active elements will instead have the aria-disabled attribute set accordingly. The specified elements will also be tracked internally. When a link or simulated active element is disabled, the specified elements will continue to receive focus.

Example:

// The first parameter may be set to a DOM node, an array of DOM nodes, a CSS selector, or a DC object.

$A.setDisabled(domElement, true);

// Or

$A.setDisabled(domElement, false);
