
Function: updateDisabled(domElementArrayOrDC)

Description: Tracks all specified elements to prevent their associated DC objects from rendering when activated.

Returns: Original Object, or $A object if chained.

Note: The updateDisabled() function is meant to automatically set or unset the disabled flag on associated DC objects for tracking; it will not change the disabled state on any active elements. To change the disabled state of 1 or more active elements, use the setDisabled() function.

Example:

// Update the disabled state of an element.
$A.updateDisabled(domElement);

// Update the disabled state of an array of elements.
$A.updateDisabled(domElementArray);

// Update the disabled state of an array of DC objects.
$A.updateDisabled(dcObjectArray);

// Update the disabled state of all elements in the DOM that include aria-disabled="true".
$A.updateDisabled();
