
Function: getAccName(domElement)

Description: Returns the accessible name computation for both the Name and Description properties in accordance with the latest W3C AccName Prototype algorithm.

Returns: Object with properties: "name", "desc", and "error"

Requires module: "AccName"

Note: This is not the same as the getText() method, but rather explicitly follows the algorithm specified in the AccName computation for computing Names and Descriptions within the accessibility tree. In accordance with the W3C AccName specification, an element may only have an accessible name if it meets the definition of specific criteria. The getAccName function does not support chaining.
For further details regarding the AccName algorithm, visit: https://github.com/whatsock/w3c-alternative-text-computation

Example:

$A.import("AccName", { defer: true }, function() {

  // Compute the name and description of a form field
  var accessible = $A.getAccName(domElement);

  // Show the accessible name.
  alert( accessible.name );

  // Show the accessible description.
  alert( accessible.desc );

});
