
Function: skipTo(skipLinkElementOrCSSSelector, targetElementOrCSSSelector, objectConfig, functionOverride)

Description: Sets a handler on an element to move focus to the specified target element using a smooth scroll animation when clicked.

Returns: domElement, or $A object if chained.

Requires module: "SmoothScroll"

Note: The objectConfig parameter can be used to change the default options for the skip link functionality. The functionOverride parameter can be used to change the default focus movement statement to perform a different action instead. If a functionOverride is specified, a similare $A.focus(target) statement must be included within the animation callback to ensure accessibility for keyboard users.

Example:

$A.import("SmoothScroll", { defer: true }, function() {

  // Set a skip link to move to a target element when clicked.
  $A(domElement).skipTo(domElementTarget);

  // Or using CSS selectors
  $A("a.skip-link-cls").skipTo("#target-id");

  // Set a skip link and change configuration options.
  // View the SetSkipLink help doc to see available configuration options.

  $A("a.skip-link-cls").skipTo(domElementTarget, {
    skipReturn: true,
    override: {
      duration: 750,
      easing: "ease-in"
    }
  });

});
