
Function: updateDisabled(domElementArrayOrDC)

Description: Tracks all specified elements to prevent their associated DC objects from rendering when activated.

Returns: Original Object, or $A object if chained.

Note: The updateDisabled() function is meant to automatically set or unset the disabled flag on associated DC objects for tracking; it will not change the disabled state on any active elements. To change the disabled state of 1 or more active elements, use the setDisabled() function.

Example:

$A.updateDisabled(domElementArray);

// Or

$A.updateDisabled(dcObjectArray);
