
DC.prependTo(domElementOrCSSSelector, objectKeyValueMap)

Description: Inserts DC.wrapper at the beginning of a DOM element or CSS selector referenced element.

Returns: DC Object.

Note: The objectKeyValueMap may include optional DC object declaration overrides that will be applied to the DC object prior to rendering.

Example:

// Insert DC.wrapper at the beginning of a DOM element.
DC.prependTo(domElement);

// Insert DC.wrapper at the beginning of one element referenced by a CSS selector.
DC.prependTo("#targetNode");

// Insert DC.wrapper at the beginning of a DOM element and include DC API overrides.
DC.prependTo(domElement, {
  // Declarative DC API properties and methods.
});
