
Function: isDisabled(domElementOrDC)

Description: Checks if an element or a DC object is disabled.

Returns: True if yes, False otherwise.

Note: Meant to accompany the updateDisabled() function. Will return true if a native form field is disabled, or if an element has a bound DC object that is disabled, or if an element includes the attribute aria-disabled="true".

Example:

var disabled = $A.isDisabled(domNode);

if (disabled) return;
