
Function: isOutOfView(domElement)

Description: Determines if a rendered element is partially or totally scrolled offscreen so that its full content is not displayed in the viewport.

Returns: Object with properties: "bounding", "top", "left", "right", "bottom", "any", and "all".

Note: The "bounding" property returns the getBoundingClientRect object that all other properties are computed from. All other properties are of type Boolean. When a returned Boolean property is true, it is not visible in the viewport. Otherwise, the element is visible in the viewport if its Boolean property is false.

Example:

// Get the bounding props for an element.
var outOfBounds = $A.isOutOfView(domElement);

// Check if the bottom edge of the element is scrolled offscreen.
if (outOfBounds.bottom) {
  // Scroll the viewport vertically to account for the offscreen content and bring it into view.
  window.scrollBy(0, (window.innerHeight || document.documentElement.clientHeight) - outOfBounds.bounding.bottom);
}
