
Function: setCircularTabbing(domContainerElement)

Shorthand: setCircTab(domContainerElement)

Description: Sets circular tabbing for all focusable active elements within the specified DOM container element.

Returns: Array of focusable active elements, or $A object if chained.

Note: When set, using the Tab key to move focus from one focusable element to another will move back to the first focusable element in the container, and the same in reverse when pressing Shift+Tab to go backwards. This is often used for dialogs or temporary content panels that can be closed to resume normal focus movement afterwards.

Example:

// Set circular tabbing within a specific container element.
var focusableElementsArray = $A.setCircularTabbing(domContainerElement);

// Or the same using chaining

// Set circular tabbing within a specific container element.
var myChain = $A(domContainerElement).setCircularTabbing();

// To return the modified object within a chain, use the "return()" method.

var myObject = myChain.return();
