
Function: svgFix(domElementOrCSSSelector)

Description: Fixes all SVG elements within the specified container so they won't appear in the tab order when viewed in IE.

Returns: Original Object, or $A object if chained.

Note: When IE is detected, the focusable attribute on all SVG elements will be set to "true" to ensure accessibility for screen reader and keyboard-only users.

Example:

$A.svgFix(domContainerElement);
