
DC.nearestHeadingLevel(context)

Shorthand: DC.nearestHL(context)

Description: Returns the number of the closest heading level in the reading order relative to the DC.wrapper element.

Returns: Number.

Note: If context is not specified, window.document will be used instead. If there are no headings prior to DC.wrapper in the reading order, 0 will be returned. Both native H1 through H6 headings and ARIA headings are recognized equally.

Example:

DC.nearestHeadingLevel();
