
DC.updateDisabled()

Description: Updates the disabled state for one or more DC objects based on the disabled state of the triggering element.

Returns: DC Object.

Note: All associated sibling DC objects will be updated when updateDisabled() is executed. The disabled state is true when the triggering element consists of a native active element with a disabled state, or when the triggering element includes aria-disabled="true".

Example:

// Update the disabled state for all associated sibling DC objects based on their triggering elements.
DC.updateDisabled();
