
DC.activeElements

Description: Contains an array of all focusable active elements within the DC object content after it is rendered. If no focusable active elements are detected, the DC.activeElements property will be set to an empty array.

Returns: Array.

Example:

// Loop through all focusable active elements and perform an action on each.
$A.loop(DC.activeElements, function(index, element) {
  // Do something.
}, "array");
