
Function: query(stringCSSSelectorOrNodeArray, functionFilterCallback(key, value))

Description: Processes a filtered list of matching elements and returns an array of nodes.

Returns: filtered Array.

Note: The query() function will always return an array, even when empty.

The callback function that executes on every object in the array also acts as a filter. By returning false from the callback, it will prevent that object from being returned as part of the final array returned from the DC.query() function.

Example:

// Get an array of matching elements within the DC object container.
var myArray = DC.query("h1, h2, h3");

// Process an array of elements within the DC object container.
var myArray = DC.query("button.toggle", function(index, object) {
  // Do something with each object.
});

// Process an array of elements and filter specific objects so they are not returned as part of the final array.
var myArray = DC.query("button.toggle", function(index, element) {
  // Prevent disabled buttons from being added to myArray when returned.
  return (element.disabled) ? false : true;
});
