
DC.remove(optionalCallbackFunction)

Description: Removes all rendered elements and exicutes relevant lifecycle methods on the DC object.

Returns: DC Object.

Note: When DC.animate.onRemove is set to a valid function, it will apply related visual effects before the process of removal completes. An optional function can be passed as the first parameter to execute a temporary one-time callback after the removal process completes.

Example:

// Optionally apply a visual animation effect before the DC object is closed.
DC.animate.onRemove = function(DC, outerNode, complete) {
  // To ensure accessibility, make sure that the complete() function is executed within the callback after the animation finishes.
  complete();
};

// Close the DC object and remove all rendered content.
DC.remove();

// Remove the DC object content and execute a one-time callback.
DC.remove(function() {
  // Do stuff.
  alert(DC.id);
});
