
DC.toggle(optionalCallbackFunction)

Description: Toggles the DC object between render or remove and exicutes relevant lifecycle methods.

Returns: DC Object.

Note: An optional function can be passed as the first parameter to execute a temporary one-time callback after the rendering or removal process completes.

Example:

DC.toggle();

// Toggle the DC object content and execute a one-time callback.
DC.toggle(function() {
  // Do stuff.
  alert(DC.id);
});
