
Function: isArray(object)

Description: Determines if an object is a valid Array.

Returns: True if yes, False otherwise.

Note: This function does not perform the same check as the Array.isArray() method. Instead, $A.isArray() will check if the object is a valid iterable array-like object, which is necessary to determine if the object can be processed in the same manner as a standard Array. As such, $A.isArray() will return true if the object is a normal array with an object type of "[object Array]", "[object NodeList]", or "[object HTMLCollection]", which then allows for the processing of DOM node arrays in the same manner as a standard Array. The isArray() function always returns a Boolean value, even when chained.

Example:

// Is an object a valid iterable Array
var confirm = $A.isArray(object);
