
String: moduleFolder

Description: Specifies the directory where 4X module files are stored on the server.

Note: The correct module path must be set for 4X to function correctly. The default value for $A.moduleFolder is "/4X/Modules/", which specifies that the 4X folder is available at the root of the webserver folder structure. If the folder name or file path is changed, then $A.moduleFolder must be changed to reflect the correct module file path.

Example:

// Change the value of $A.moduleFolder to reference a different folder path where modules are stored.
// E.G. Assuming that these are now stored at: www.myDomain.com/scripting/4X/Modules
$A.moduleFolder = "/scripting/4X/Modules/";

// This can also be changed by updating the "moduleFolder" property within 4X.js as well.
