
DC.render(optionalCallbackFunction)

Description: Renders DC object content and exicutes relevant lifecycle methods.

Returns: DC Object.

Note: When DC.animate.onRender is set to a valid function, it will apply related visual effects before the final process of opening completes. An optional function can be passed as the first parameter to execute a temporary one-time callback after the rendering process completes.

Example:

// Optionally apply a visual animation effect as the DC object is opening.
DC.animate.onRender = function(DC, wrapper, next) {
  // To ensure accessibility, make sure that the next() function is executed within the callback after the animation finishes.
  next();
};

// Open the DC object and render its content.
DC.render();

// Render the DC object content and execute a one-time callback.
DC.render(function() {
  // Do stuff.
  alert(DC.id);
});
