
DC.rerender(optionalCallbackFunction)

Description: Rerenders DC object content and exicutes relevant lifecycle methods.

Returns: DC Object.

Note: If the DC object is already open, DC.remove() will be exicuted before DC.render(), and all relevant lifecycle handlers will be exicuted. An optional function can be passed as the first parameter to execute a temporary one-time callback after the rendering process completes.

Example:

DC.rerender();

// Rerender the DC object content and execute a one-time callback.
DC.rerender(function() {
  // Do stuff.
  alert(DC.id);
});
