
Function: hasDC(stringIdOrObject, boolIncludeFromBound)

Description: Checks if a string or object has a bound registered DC object.

Returns: Boolean: true if found, false otherwise.

Note: When only the first parameter is populated, hasDC() will only return true if the specified object is set as the id of a registered DC object. When boolIncludeFromBound is true, hasDC() will also return true if bound to the specified object.

Example:

// Check if a string is set as the DC.id of a registered DC object
var hasBoundDC = $A.hasDC("UniqueStringID");

// Check if a DOM element is set as the DC.id of a registered DC object
var hasBoundDC = $A.hasDC(domElement);

// Check if a triggering element has a bound DC object.
var hasBoundDC = $A.hasDC(domElement, true);

// Or

var hasBoundDC = $A(domElement).hasDC(true);
