
Function: lastCreatedCallback(functionCallback(lastCreatedArray))

Description: Sets a callback function to be exicuted after the most recent array of DC objects is created.

Returns: Null.

Note: The callback function will only exicute once before it is automatically deleted. The lastCreated array is passed to the callback as the first argument. The lastCreatedCallback() function does not support chaining.

Example:

$A.lastCreatedCallback(function(lastCreatedArray) {
  // Do something with lastCreatedArray.
});
