
Function: getText(domElement)

Description: Returns the inner text content of a DOM node.

Returns: String.

Note: The getText() function will only return the inner text of an element, not including any alternative text that is added using element attributes such as title, alt, aria-label, aria-labelledby, nor aria-owns. To return the accessible name computation instead, use the getAccName() function as documented in ARIA Development.

Example:

var textString = $A.getText(domElement);

// Or the same using chaining

var textString = $A(domElement).getText();
