
Function: announce(stringOrElementNode, boolDoNotRepeat)

Description: Performs an unobtrusive announcement for screen reader users using a string message or the textual contents of a DOM element.

Returns: String, domElement, or $A object if chained.

Note: Designed to function automatically within screen readers that properly support ARIA live regions. The announce method is also prototyped to the String object for alternative usage. Method supports auto-queuing for rapid succession such as within live chat applications. Uses aria-live="polite" to prevent speech interruption when queued.

Example:

// Basic announcement of textual content within a DOM element.
var myElement = $A.announce(domElement);

// Announce a string message while suppressing repeat text
var stringVariable = $A.announce(stringMessage, true);

// Using strings

// Basic announcement of a string object
var stringVariable = "Downloading, please wait.".announce();

// Announce a string object while suppressing repeat text
stringVariable.announce(true);

// Manually clear the internal message queue

$A.announce.clear();

// Or

stringVariable.announce.clear();
