
Function: owns(domElementOrCSSSelector, child-domElementOrCSSSelector)

Description: Sets up an accessible parent child relationship between elements within the accessibility tree.

Returns: Original Object, or $A object if chained.

Note: The owns() function will automatically configure a valid ARIA parent child relationship, even if the child elements do not include an id. It will automatically manage the aria-owns attribute accordingly. If the owning element cannot support the aria-owns relationship accessibly, as is the case with "input", "img", "progress", "iframe", and "hr" elements, the attribute will not be set to ensure accessibility with assistive technologies. For an example of this functionality in action, view the Tree module template.

WARNING: Use of the aria-owns attribute will change the reading order of the accessibility tree for assistive technology users, and can cause critical accessibility issues when implemented improperly. Extreme care must always be taken when using this feature.

Example:

$A.owns(domElement, domElementChild);

$A.owns("#listbox-id", "div.option");

// Or the same using chaining

$A(domElement).owns(domElementChild);

$A("#listbox-id").owns("div.option");
