
Function: $A(domElementOrMarkupStringOrCSSSelector)

Description: Create and return a $A Chain Object.

Returns: $A Chain Object.

Note: All Chain objects map to the $A (4X) API, and can be chained together to create complex chaining statements. If the argument passed to $A() is bound as the ID of a DC object however, the DC object will be returned instead. When a DC object is returned, it then maps to the DC API. When chained, string markup will automatically be converted into a DOM node fragment, or CSS selectores will query the targetted elements to reference those that match.

Example:

// Create a chain object using a DOM element.
var myChain = $A(domElement);

// Create a chain object using a CSS selector to locate the first div with the class "errorSection", and move focus to it.
var myChain = $A("div.errorSection").focus();

// Create a DOM fragment ready for chaining with additional methods.
var myChain = $A('<button class="toggleBtn">Settings</button>')
// Then set attributes on the new object stored within the chain.
.setAttribute({
  "aria-pressed": "false"
})
// Then bind events to the object within the chain.
.on({
  click: function(e) {
    $A(this).toggleClass("pressed", function(stateIsTrue) {
      // Change associated attribute to match the toggle class state from within the callback.
      $A(this).setAttribute("aria-pressed", stateIsTrue ? "true" : "false");
    });
  }
})
// Then insert the new object as modified before the first H1 element on the page using a CSS selector.
  .before("h1");

// Return the modified object within a chain.
var domElement = myChain.return();
