
Function: isPointerWithin(domContainerElement)

Description: Checks if the mouse pointer is contained within the specified container element.

Returns: True if yes, False otherwise.

Note: If domContainerElement is not specified, it will default to document.body.

Example:

// Verify if the mouse pointer is contained within a DOM element.
var isWithinNode = $A.isPointerWithin(domElement);
