
Function: owns(domElementOrCSSSelector, child-domElementOrCSSSelector)

Description: Sets up an accessible parent child relationship between elements within the accessibility tree.

Returns: Original Object, or $A object if chained.

Note: The owns() function will automatically configure a valid ARIA parent child relationship, even if the child elements do not include an id. If the owning element cannot support the aria-owns relationship accessibly, as is the case with "input", "img", "progress", "iframe", and "hr" elements, the attribute will not be set to ensure accessibility with assistive technologies. For an example of this functionality in action, view the Tree module template.

Example:

$A.owns(domElement, domElementChild);

$A.owns("#listbox-id", "div.option");

// Or the same using chaining

$A(domElement).owns(domElementChild);

$A("#listbox-id").owns("div.option");
