
DC.clearOffScreen()

Description: Clears all previously applied offscreen styling from DC.wrapper.

Returns: DC Object.

Note: Offscreen styling is used to display element content to screen reader users that does not appear visually on the screen. The clearOffScreen function will unset all styling properties previously set using DC.setOffScreen, causing this content to become visible.

Example:

DC.clearOffScreen();
