
DC.isAnimating

Description: Determines if an animation effect is currently running as part of the current DC object lifecycle.

Returns: True if yes, False otherwise.

Note: This property is only set when a valid animation effect is active within a DC object declaration. For further details, see: 
Help/DC API/DC Object Configuration/Visual Effects

Example:

// Is an animation effect currently running on the DC object?

var disabled = DC.isAnimating;
