
DC.toggleClass(stringClassName, boolForceState, functionCallback(currentState))

Description: Toggles a class name on DC.wrapper.

Returns: DC Object.

Note: When the boolForceState parameter is omitted, DC.toggleClass will automatically toggle itself using the current state. Otherwise, the boolForceState parameter will force a true or false state to be set. The callback function may be used to perform additional actions relating to the toggle state. When the callback function is passed as the second parameter, then boolForceState is undefined.

Example:

// Automatically toggle between true or false based on the current state of the class name on DC.wrapper.
DC.toggleClass("selected");

// Automatically toggle the state to true and set class name on DC.wrapper.
DC.toggleClass("selected", true);

// Automatically toggle between true or false based on the current state of the class name on DC.wrapper, and run a callback to perform additional actions.
DC.toggleClass("selected", function(activeState) {
  // Do something when activeState is true or false.
  // 'this' = DC.wrapper.
});

// Automatically toggle the state to false and remove class name on DC.wrapper, and run a callback to perform additional actions.
DC.toggleClass("selected", false, function(activeState) {
  // Do something when activeState is true or false.
  // 'this' = DC.wrapper.
});
