
Function: scrollTo(domElementOrCSSSelector, objectConfig, functionOverride)

Description: Scrolls to the specified element using a smooth scroll animation.

Returns: domElement, or $A object if chained.

Requires module: "SmoothScroll"

Note: The scrollTo() function does not move keyboard focus, and must not be used as a skip link handler for this purpose. Instead, the scrollTo() function is ideal when combined with the use of aria-activedescendant, when the referenced element must be scrolled into view, but keyboard focus remains on the same element as before. The objectConfig parameter can be used to change the default options for the Velocity animation effect.

Example:

$A.import("SmoothScroll", { defer: true }, function() {

  // Scroll to a target element.
  $A.scrollTo(domElement);

  // Scroll to a target element and change the animation configuration options.
  $A.scrollTo(domElement, {
    duration: 750,
    easing: "ease-in"
  });

});
