
DC.focus()

Description: Forces progrommatic focus to the beginning of DC.outerNode, or to the first focusable active element within the DC.activeElements array.

Returns: DC Object.

Note: This method moves programmatic focus, and does not explicitly set or trigger any attached focus handlers. When dc.forceFocusWithin is set to false, focus will be set to the DC object container element. Otherwise, focus will be set to the first active element within the container.

Example:

DC.focus();
