
DC.speak(boolIsAlert)

Description: Performs an unobtrusive announcement for supporting screen readers using the textual contents of DC.container.

Returns: DC Object.

Note: DC.speak() is designed to function automatically within screen readers that properly support ARIA live regions. The DC.speak() function supports auto-queuing for rapid succession such as within live chat applications. When boolIsAlert is set to true, the announced content will be processed as a role=alert message that will fire a system alert when invoked. The boolIsAlert property must not be set to true when implementing multiple objects to fire in succession, otherwise only the last message will be recognized by screen reader users.

Example:

DC.speak();
