
DC.updateDisabled(objectDC)

Description: Updates the disabled state for one or more DC objects based on the disabled state of the triggering element.

Returns: DC Object.

Note: When objectDC is passed as a valid DC object instance, only the disabled state for that DC object will be updated. Otherwise, all associated sibling DC objects will be updated. The disabled state is true when the triggering element consists of a native active element with a disabled state, or when the triggering element includes aria-disabled="true".

Example:

// Update the disabled state for all associated sibling DC objects based on their triggering elements.
DC.updateDisabled();

// Update the disabled state for the current DC object based on its triggering element.
DC.updateDisabled(DC);
