
Function: hideBackground(domElementToExclude)

Description: Removes background content from the accessibility tree so that non-sighted screen reader users cannot perceive it during navigation.

Returns: domElement, or $A object if chained.

Note: The hideBackground() function has no impact on visual layout, but rather, will prevent background content from being perceived or navigated by non-sighted screen reader users. This function includes safety features to ensure that the accidental hiding of the entire page from screen reader users cannot occur. If domElementToExclude references an element that is not in the correct DOM location to ensure accessibility, it will automatically be appended to document.body to ensure accessibility for non-sighted screen reader users. If no domElementToExclude is specified, nothing will be hidden.

Example:

// Hide the background content so that only the foreground dialog container element is perceivable and navigable for non-sighted screen reader users.

$A.hideBackground(dialogContainerElementToExclude);
