
Boolean: isTouch

Description: Determines if the current page has been interacted with by touch or by use of the keyboard.

Returns: True if yes, False otherwise.

Note: The touchChange event fires when this property changes between true or false, which can be used to perform specific actions when a user action change is detected.

Example:

// Has the page been touched?
alert($A.isTouch);
