
DC.hasClass(stringClassName)

Description: Checks if one or more space delimited class names exist on DC.outerNode.

Returns: Boolean: true if found, false otherwise.

Note: If more than one class name is listed in the second parameter, DC.hasClass will only return true if all of the specified class names exist within the specified element. The DC.hasClass() function always returns a Boolean value, even when chained.

Example:

var alreadyHasClass = DC.hasClass("selected-option");
