
DC.insertWithin(domElementOrCSSSelector, objectKeyValueMap)

Description: Inserts DC.outerNode within a DOM element or CSS selector referenced element.

Returns: DC Object.

Note: Before DC.outerNode is inserted within the target element, all preexisting content will be cleaned and removed to prevent memory leaks. The objectKeyValueMap may include optional DC object declaration overrides that will be applied to the DC object prior to rendering.

Example:

// Insert DC.outerNode within a DOM element.
DC.insertWithin(domElement);

// Insert DC.outerNode within one element referenced by a CSS selector.
DC.insertWithin("#targetNode");

// Insert DC.outerNode within a DOM element and include DC API overrides.
DC.insertWithin(domElement, {
  // Declarative DC API properties and methods.
});
