
DC.remove()

Description: Removes all rendered elements and exicutes relevant lifecycle methods on the DC object.

Returns: DC Object.

Note: When DC.animate.onRemove is set to a valid function, it will apply related visual effects before the process of removal completes.

Example:

// Optionally apply a visual animation effect before the DC object is closed.
DC.animate.onRemove = function(DC, outerNode, complete) {
  // To ensure accessibility, make sure that the complete() function is executed within the callback after the animation finishes.
  complete();
};

// Close the DC object and remove all rendered content.
DC.remove();
