
DC.render()

Description: Renders DC object content and exicutes relevant lifecycle methods.

Returns: DC Object.

Note: When DC.animate.onRender is set to a valid function, it will apply related visual effects before the final process of opening completes.

Example:

// Optionally apply a visual animation effect as the DC object is opening.
DC.animate.onRender = function(DC, outerNode, complete) {
  // To ensure accessibility, make sure that the complete() function is executed within the callback after the animation finishes.
  complete();
};

// Open the DC object and render its content.
DC.render();
