
Event: "load"

Description: Sets a handler to exicute when the page content completes loading.

Returns: domElement, or $A object if chained.

Note: Since this event is always on the window object, there is no specific target element needed when setting this event handler. When this event is set, it will automatically check if the page content is already loaded, and will execute immediately if so. Otherwise, the load event will be bound to the window object.

Example:

// Bind a load handler to the window object.

$A.on("load", function(event) {
  // Do something.
});
