
Event: "touchChange"

Description: Sets a handler to exicute when user interaction switches from keyboard to touch and from touch to keyboard.

Returns: domElement, or $A object if chained.

Note: Since this event is always on the window object, there is no specific target element needed when setting this event handler. When this event fires, $A.isTouch will reflect the new value true or false depending on the type of user action that was detected.

Example:

// Bind a touch change handler to the window object.

$A.on("touchChange", function(event) {
  // Do something when the property $A.isTouch changes between true or false.
});
