
Function: getDC(stringIdOrObject, boolIncludeFromBound)

Description: Return the registered DC object bound to a specific string ID or object.

Returns: DC Object.

Note: ID refers to the matching DC.id property value of a registered DC object. The ID of a DC object must always be unique. Since getDC() is a default function for $A, the syntax $A(stringOrObjectID) will perform the same action as $A.getDC(stringOrObjectID). After a DC object is returned, only valid properties and methods specified in the DC API are available on that object. When boolIncludeFromBound is true, the bound DC object will be returned if present on the specified object.

Example:

// Get the registered DC object with DC.id = "myDCObjectID"
var DC = $A.getDC("myDCObjectID");

// Get the registered DC object where DC.id is set to a DOM element.
var DC = $A.getDC(domElement);

// Get the DC object bound to a triggering element.
var DC = $A.getDC(trigger, true);

// Or the same using chaining

// Get the registered DC object with DC.id = "myDCObjectID"
var DC = $A("myDCObjectID");

// Get the registered DC object where DC.id is set to a DOM element as its trigger.
var DC = $A(domElement);

// Get the DC object bound to a triggering element.
var DC = $A(trigger).getDC(true);
