
Function: mergeGlobal()

Description: Retroactively merges newly declared global DC properties and methods into all registered DC objects.

Returns: Null.

Note: setGlobal() must be invoked before mergeGlobal is applied. Merging only applies to previously instantiated DC objects. All properties and methods that are explicitly set within individual DC objects will not be overwritten to preserve the local configuration of those objects.

Example:

$A.mergeGlobal();
