
Function: queryDC(arrayOfIds, functionFilterCallback(DC))

Description: Searches through all registered DC objects and performs a callback function on each match to filter the returned array.

Returns: DC Object Array.

Note: When arrayOfIds is specified, the loop action will only search through the DC objects that are bound to the ids within that array. Otherwise, all registered DC objects will be searched and the filter function will be applied to each. To prevent a DC object from being added to the returned array, return false must be added to the filter callback function. The queryDC() function does not support chaining.

Example:

// Perform a callback on each registered DC object.
$A.queryDC(function(DC) {
  // Do something with DC
});

// Search through all registered DC objects that are bound to the ids specified in the first parameter and perform a callback on each matching DC object.
$A.queryDC([
  "id1", "id2", "id3"
], function(DC) {
  // Do something with DC
});

// Search through all registered DC objects and return an array that matches the filter directive.
var myDialogs = $A.queryDC(function(DC) {
  return (dc.widgetType === "Dialog");
});
