
Function: setGlobal(objectKeyValueMap, boolMergeRetroactively)

Description: Sets global properties and methods that will be prototyped into all new DC objects when registered.

Returns: Null.

Note: When boolMergeRetroactively is set to true, $A.mergeGlobal() will automatically be invoked after the new global properties and methods are saved. Otherwise, the specified properties and methods will only be prototyped into new DC objects when registered. The setGlobal() function will not prevent or overwrite the local configuration of individual DC objects.

Example:

// Set new global properties and methods for use within all newly generated DC objects.
$A.setGlobal({
  props: {
    serverEnabled: true,
    loadFromServer: function() {
      var dc = this.DC;
      if (dc.props.serverEnabled) {
        $A.get({
          url: "server/api/json?params",
          data: {returnType: "json"},
          success: function(json, promise) {
            // Process json and build markup to render within content var.
            var content = "Whatever"; // populate with JSON data however.
            // Set content as source for the current DC object.
            dc.source = content;
            // Prevent this object from contacting the server a second time if successful.
            dc.props.serverEnabled = false;
            // Now render the DC object and display the new data.
            dc.render();
          }
        });
      }
      return dc;
    }
  }
});

// Set new global properties and methods for use within all generated DC objects, including previously instantiated ones.
$A.setGlobal({
  props: {
    serverEnabled: true,
    loadFromServer: function() {
      var dc = this.DC;
      if (dc.props.serverEnabled) {
        // Do something as shown above, then render using dc.render().
      }
      return dc;
    }
  }
}, true);
